Guide to the Horace Walpole Collection
The Lewis Walpole Library
- Horace Walpole's Correspondence, 1725-1797; Series I; 12
  - North, Lady Anne
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1793 Nov 30 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 396. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 341.
  - Northumberland, Elizabeth, Duchess (Countess) of
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1759 [Mar 19?] (Box 34, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 162. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 160.
  - Onslow, Arthur
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Aug 5 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 98. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 144.
  - Ossory, Anne, Countess of Upper *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1777 Oct 30 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 32, p. 391-93.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1779 Oct 14 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 33, p. 124.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1782 Feb 28 (Box 34, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 33, p. 330.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, Circa 1782 Mar 21 (Box 34, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 33, p. 331-32.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1791 Feb 14 (Box 34, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 34, p. 107-8.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1793 July 16 (Box 34, Folder 33a)
      Yale Edition, v. 34, p. 182-4.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Draft in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1797 Jan 15 (Box 34, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 34, p. 230-31.
  - Ossory, John, Earl of Upper *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1773 Oct 12 (Box 34, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 32, p. 157.
  - Panton, Paul
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Enclosure only), 1789 Jun 24 (Box 34, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 43, p. 164. Not in Toynbee.
  - Parker, Mark *
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1740 Sep 24 NS (Box 34, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 26, Appendix 1. Not in Toynbee.
      With other documents about Horace Walpole's purchases in Italy.
  - Paxton, Rev. William
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Address only), 1792 Jan 31 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Pearce, Rev. Zachary
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Jul 10 (Box 34, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 200-202. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 120-22.
  - Pelham, Hon. Henry
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jul 16 OS (Box 34, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 39-40. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Draft in Horace Walpole's hand), 1752 Nov 25 (Box 34, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 73. Toynbee iii, p. 132-33.
  - Pennant, Thomas *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1773 May 17 (Box 34, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 250. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1773 May 25 (Box 34, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 251-54. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1779 Jan 9 (Box 34, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 394-95. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1781 Oct 15 (Box 34, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 442-46. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1782 Jun 13 (Box 34, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 16-17. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1782 Jun 23 (Box 34, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 19-21. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1782 Oct 15 (Box 34, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 37-39. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1787 Oct 10 (Box 34, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 198-99. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1788 Apr 20 (Box 34, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 214-15. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 50-52.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1788 Apr 30 (Box 34, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 216-17. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1789 Mar 30 (Box 34, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 234-36. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1790 Apr 19 (Box 34, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 278-79. Not in Toynbee.
  - Percy, Rev. Thomas
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1792 Aug 20 (Box 34, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 369-70. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 56-57.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1792 Sep 18 (Box 34, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 378-83. Toynbee xv, p. 147-50.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1793 Oct 15 (Box 34, Folder 56)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 394-96. Not in Toynbee.
  - Pinkerton, John *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1784 Oct 6 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      See note in Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 255.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Copy, probably in the hand of the wife or a daughter of Dawson Turner), 1784 Oct 6 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 255-58.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1785 Mar 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 262.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1785 Jun 22 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 263-67.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1785 Jun 26 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 267-73.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1785 Jul 27 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 274-75.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1785 Aug 18 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 276-77.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1785 Sep 17 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 278-81.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1785 Oct 2 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 284-85.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1785 Oct 9 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 286.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1785 Dec 9 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 287-88.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1786 Oct 18 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 289-90.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1786 Nov 29 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 290-91.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1787 Jan 22 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 291.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1787 Jun 29 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 291-94.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1788 Feb 11 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 294-95.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1789 July 31 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 302-5.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1789 Aug 14 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 305-8. Yale Edition, v. 43, p. 228-29. Toynbee xiv, p. 189.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1789 Aug 19 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 308-9.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1790 May 26 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 311-12.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1791 Dec 26 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 312-15.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1793 Sep 25 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 317-18.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1793 Oct 22 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1794 Mar 2 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 318-19.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1794 Apr 4 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 383.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1794 Apr 11 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 319.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1795 Jan 25 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 320-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1795 Feb 3 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 325-26.
  - Pitt, Thomas *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1764 Jun 5 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 330-37. Toynbee vi, p. 68-77.
  - Pitt, William, 1st Earl of Chatham
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Feb 27 (Box 35, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 92. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 99.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1759 Nov 20 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 172-73. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 162-63.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Jan 7 (Box 35, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 190-91. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 118.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Aug 30 (Box 35, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 356. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 127.
  - Pope, Elizabeth
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1781 Oct 22 (Box 35, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 446-47. Toynbee Supp. i, p. 282-83.
  - Pownall, Thomas *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1783 Oct 27 (Box 35, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 77-82. Toynbee xiii, p. 73-77.
  - Poyntz, Stephen
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1747 Jul 1 OS (Box 35, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 58-59. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 88.
  - Queensberry, Catherine Douglas, Duchess of
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, [177-?] (Box 35, Folder 35a)
      Existence and Location of Originals
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 469. Toynbee Supp. iIi, p. 316.
  - Ramsay, Allan
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1759 (Box 35, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 150. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 163-64.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 (Box 35, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 370. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 316-17.
  - Ratcliffe, John *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1762 [mid-March?] (Box 35, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 235-37. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 248-49.
  - Reade, Henry
    - To (?) Henry Reade, letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1760 (Box 35, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 174. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 May 1 (Box 35, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 191-92. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 97-98.
      With enclosure: 'Copy of the Schedule of Baron de Newhoff,' dated 24 June 1755.
  - Reed, Isaac
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1774 Nov 11 (Box 35, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 280-81. Toynbee ix, p. 88-89.
  - Rena, Contessa
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1763 Apr 9 (Box 35, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 280. Toynbee v, p. 309-10.
  - Richmond, Charles, 3d Duke of
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 May 9 (Box 35, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 299-302. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1775 Oct 27 (Box 35, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 310-17. Toynbee ix, p. 274-76.
  - [Richmond, Mary, Duchess of?]
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, [Between 1784 and 1791?] (Box 35, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 470. Not in Toynbee.
  - Robertson, Walter
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Feb 18 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Rogers, Charles
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1782 Apr 18 (Box 35, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 9. Not in Toynbee.
  - Roscoe, William *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1795 Apr 4 (Box 35, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 259.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1795 Apr 27 (Box 35, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 264.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), Circa 1796 Jul 12 (Box 35, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 439-40.
  - Ryves, Elizabeth
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, [1776?] (Box 35, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 329. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 340.
  - Saint-Simon, Marquis de
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1755 Jul 19 (Box 35, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 82-83. Not in Toynbee.
  - Sawbridge, Catharine (Catharine Macaulay) *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1773 Mar 30 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Selwyn, George *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1749 Sep 22 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 117-18.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1755 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 124.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1757 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 133.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1757 Oct 2 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 113. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1757 Oct 5 [i.e. 6] (Box 36, Folder 4a)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 139-40.
      Purchased at auction, Swann Galleries, 20 November 2014.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1757 Oct 8 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 140-41.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1757 Oct 11 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 141-43.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1758 Aug 22 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 148-49.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1758 Nov-1761 May (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 151.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1759 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 151.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1759 Jun 9 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 163. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, [1760?] Oct 21 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 161.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1761 Mar 21 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 163-65.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1762 Aug 31 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 165-66.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1763 Sep 28 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 171-72.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, [Between 1767 and 1786] (Box 36, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 281.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1767 Apr-May (Box 36, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 244.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1767 Oct 16 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 250-52.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1770 [Apr 12?] (Box 36, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 253-54.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1773 Apr 5 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 259.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1775 Jul 8 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 261-62.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1775 Sep 16 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 262-66.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1780 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 276.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1785 Jan [27?] (Box 36, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 277-78.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole ("If you and ..."), No Date (Box 36, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 282-83.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole ("Dr. King has ..."), No Date (Box 36, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 283.
  - Seroux d'Agincourt, Jean-Baptiste-Louis-Georges
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (in the hand of a secretary), 1783 Jul 20 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 63-69. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 284-88.
  - Seton, Barbara Cecilia
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1790 Nov 13 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 11, p. 137. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 63.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1790 Dec 11 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 11, p. 157-59. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 65.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1790 Dec 17 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 11, p. 166. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 68.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1790 Dec 21 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 11, p. 170-71. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 69.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1791 Aug 15 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 11, p. 333-35. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 70.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1791 Nov 11 (Box 36, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 11, p. 373-74. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 72.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1791 Nov 12 (Box 36, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 11, p. 374. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 72.
  - Sharp, John
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1759 Feb 9 (Box 36, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 158-60. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 157-58.
      With enclosures: Two copies of a letter from Edward VI to Catherine Parr, 30 May 1547.
  - Somersby, Thomas *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1773 Sep 23 (Box 36, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 262. Not in Toynbee.
  - Soyers, François de *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Address only), Circa 1784 Dec 18 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Spence, Rev. Joseph
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Oct 27 (Box 36, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 115-16. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 103-5.
  - Stanhope, Charles
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Aug 22 (Box 36, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 100. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 145.
  - Stonhewer, Richard *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1771 Sep 16 (Box 36, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 216-17.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1773 Nov 27 (Box 36, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 267-68. Toynbee xi, p. 64.
  - Strafford, 2nd Earl of *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1756 Aug 28 (Box 36, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 35, p. 278-80.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1766 Oct 4 (Box 36, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 35, p. 319-20.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, [1780?] Feb 15 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, [No year] Dec 10 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole ("I have experienced ..."), No date (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole ("I went out ..."), No date (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole ("As the taxes ..."), No date (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole ("I have been ..."), No date (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole ("I did fully ..."), No date (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Talmond, Princesse de
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Mar 18 (Box 36, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 12. Not in Toynbee.
  - Tesi, Vittoria
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1740 Dec 13 NS (Box 36, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 33. Not in Toynbee.
  - Tilson, (?)Oliver
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1779 Nov 21 (Box 36, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 405. Toynbee Supp. i, p. 278-79.
  - Townshend, Etheldreda, Viscountess *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1744 Aug 25 OS (Box 36, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 46-48. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1745 Mar (Box 36, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 51-52. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Oct 21 (Box 36, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 144. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 154-55.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1759 Sep 12 (Box 36, Folder 56)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 165-66. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1759 Sep 21 (Box 36, Folder 57)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 166-67. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1759 Oct 17 (Box 36, Folder 58)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 168. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 115.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 [Feb?] (Box 36, Folder 59)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 371. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 187-88.
  - Townshend, 1st Marquess (4th Viscount)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1772 Aug 24 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 260-61. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1791 Dec 29 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 343-45. Not in Toynbee.
  - Townshend, Hon. Mary *
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Sep 30 OS (Box 37, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 44-46. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 114-16.
  - Tyrconnel, Countess of
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, [Between 1784 and 1791] (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 472. Not in Toynbee.
  - Uguccioni, Giovanni Battista Maria *
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1740 Dec 3 NS (Box 37, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 32-33. Not in Toynbee.
  - Unknown *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Notes for a missing letter written on a playing card), Circa 1745 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1759 Feb 10 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1760 Oct 21 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1761 after Jan (Box 37, Folder 9)
      Letter possibly written to Jacques-Airmar-Henri de Moreton, Comte de Chabrillan.
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 473. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1762 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 208-9. Toynbee xv, p. 451-52.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1764 Jul 21 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Jul 25 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Extract in an unknown hand), [1766?] (Box 37, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 1. Not in Toynbee.
      Written on paper watermarked 'Hayes & Wise 1801.'
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, [1783?] May 13 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      Date based on note in Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 52.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1783 Jul 16 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 62. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Notes for a missing letter written on a playing card), Circa 1785 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Address only), 1785 Oct 14 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1788 Mar 15 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 213-14. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1792 Jul 1 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 364. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 75.
      Letter possibly written to Charles O'Hara.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1792 Jul 17 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Fragment), 1792 Nov 8 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 386. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1793 Sep 25 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      Letter possibly written to R. Lucas, Esq., of Twickenham Common.
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 393-94. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, No date (Box 37, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 474. Not in Toynbee.
      Pasted on same sheet: Small cut-out address as follows: 'To Edmund Lodge Esqre, James Street, Buckingham Gate'; franked 'Orford.'
  - Vesey, Mrs Elizabeth *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1784 Jun 18 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 99. Toynbee xiii, p. 159.
  - Viry, Contessa di
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Feb 25 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 203-4. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 221-22.
      With enclosure: Copy in Contessa di Viry's hand of Voltaire's letter to the Conde de Aranda, n.d. [July 1770].
  - Voltaire (François-Marie Arouet) *
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Copy in Jean-François Wiart's hand), 1768 Jun 6 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      See note in Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 146.
      Written on the same sheet as the French translation in Wiart's hand of Horace Walpole's letter to Voltaire, 21 June 1768.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (French translation in Jean-François Wiart's hand), 1768 Jun 21 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      See note in Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 148.
      Written on the same sheet as the copy in Wiart's hand of Horace Walpole's letter to Voltaire, 6 June 1768.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1768 Jun 21 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 148-50. Toynbee vii, p. 199-202.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Copy in Horace Walpole's hand), 1768 Jul 15 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 151-57. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Copy in Jean-Louis Wagnière's hand), 1768 Jul 15 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      See note in Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 151.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (French translation in Jean-François Wiart's hand), 1768 Jul 27 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      See note in Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 158.
  - Waldegrave, Lady Charlotte Maria (Countess of Euston)
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 May 25 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 36, p. 116-17. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 243-44.
  - Waldegrave, Hon. William
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1790 Feb 6 (Box 37, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 36, p. 272-73. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Cover only), 1795 Oct 2 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 36, p. 291. Not in Toynbee.
  - Walker, Joseph Cooper *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1789 Aug 5 (Box 37, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 253-56. Toynbee xiv, p. 179-81.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1790 Nov 6 (Box 37, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 301-2. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1790 Dec 21 (Box 37, Folder 35)